慈悲小镇·前传
编剧：托比·怀特豪斯
按照传统
Traditionally,
革命总是始于一声枪响
Revolutions begin with a gun shot,
或者战斗的号角
Or a call to arms.
但是当未来历史学家们回顾往昔
but when future historians look back
寻找卡勒的黄金时代的萌芽时
to find the seed of the golden age of the Kahler.
他们发现它始于这里
They see it began here,
始于此时
began now,
始于一个想法
began now, with an idea.
意图在于创造一种活武器
The intention is to create a living weapon.
一台全方位的战争机器
A multifaceted war machine,
永不疲倦 永不故障
that doesn't tire, doesn't malfunction.
实验对象选自于我们最后剩余的军校
The subjects were chosen from our last remaining military academy.
因为他们必须足够健康强壮
As they have to be healthy and resilient enough,
才能在改造过程中存活
to survive the procedures.
一定程度的欺骗是必要的
A degree of duplicity was necessary,
这是为了保证有人愿意参与
to secure their participation.
他们只知道自己被选中成为
They were told they've been selected for
外星殖民地的维和机器
peace keeping machines on off-world colonies.
所有的武器 雷达 和芯片
All weaponry, radar and intel,
都要完全焊接在宿主身上
will be literally fused with the host.
使得士兵和武器融为一体
So the soldier and artillery are one.
六号实验对象
Sunbject 6.
卡勒-铁克
Kahler-Tek
想法成为了现实
The idea made flesh.